（ベル坊）アイー　ダッブー
ウイー…。
（男鹿）ごきげんだな　ベル坊。
You're riding high today, Baby Beel.
アダブダー　ウィー
アダブダ…。
ん？なんだベル坊？
何言ってんだ　お前。
What, Baby Beel? What's with you?
（ホイッスル）
（姫川）いたぞ～！男鹿だ！
There he is! It's Oga!
え？何　あいつら？
おまわりさん？え…。
What's with them? Policemen?
（４人）動くな！
Don't move!
（姫川）男鹿　お前を逮捕する。
Oga, you're under arrest.
何罪だ？
What's the crime?
ザイ…それは　あれだ。
なぁ　神崎。
The crime of... you know,
that. Right, Kanzaki?
（神崎）ボケ！決まってんだろ。
ウザイだ。どや！
You know damn well your crime!
1st-degree pissin' me off!
（城山）うまいっす！神崎さん！
How's dem apples?
You tell 'em, Kanzaki-san!
（夏目）うるさい。いくよ　みんな！
Shut up. Let's go, you guys!
（４人）うぉぉ～！
てめえら　ぶっとばすぜ！
I'll blow all of you a...
じゃますんな　ベル坊！
…ってか　何でお前まで！？
（ホイッスル）
Don't get in my way, Baby Beel!
Wait, why? You, too?
なに！？なになになになになに～！
えっ　裁判所！？→
What-what-what-what?! Courthouse?
Whaddaya mean courthouse?!
Courthouse
裁判所って　なに～！？
異議あり～っ！！
Objection!
（古市）静粛に！それでは　これより「そろそろ男鹿も→
Silence in the court.
Now without further ado,
最強とか呼ばれなくて
いいんじゃねえ？だって　こいつ→
we will now start the "Isn't it about time
that we stop callin' Oga the strongest?
ボロ負けしたし～」
裁判を　とり行います。
I mean, he just got beat like chump" trial.
被告　ヘタレウンコ男鹿は前へ！
Defendant, Weak "Piece of
Shit" Oga, to the front!
俺は　やってない！俺は無実だ！
I didn't do it! I'm innocent!
（ヒルダ）裁判長　よろしいですか？
Your Honor, if I may...
（古市）被害者　ヒルデガルダ君。
Victim, Hildegarde-kun...
被告　ヘタレウンコ男鹿は今
「やってない」と証言しましたが→
The defendant, Weak POS Oga, just
testified, "I didn't do it!"
正確には「何も出来なかった」の
間違いです。よって　ここに→
But more accurately it is that
he, "couldn't do anything."
被告の呼び名を
「ヘタレウンコ男鹿」から→
Therefore, instead of calling
the defendant Weak POS Oga,
「ヘタレウンコおならプープー
弱虫男鹿」に改めることを→
I petition that he now be called
Weak POS Poopy Coward Oga.
申請します。
（アランドロン）裁判長！
Your Honor!
（古市）弁護人　アランドロン君。
Counsel Alaindelon-kun...
ウンコに行ってもいいですか？
（古市）ダメです。
Can I go take a crap?
No.
異議なし！
（古市）異議のない人は
黙っててください。
No objections!
If you don't have an objection,
don't say anything.
《くっ…これ夢か？夢だな。
何てパンチの効いた夢だ》
Is this a dream?
Gotta be a dream... This dream packs a punch!
（古市）では検察官　起訴状を。
Then would the police read the indictment?
（ラミア）
はい！起訴状　被告「ヘタレウンコ
おならプープー弱虫男鹿」は→
Yes!
Indictment:
The defendant, Weak POS Poopy Coward Oga was
once known as the strongest, the Rampaging Ogre...
最強だの　アバレオーガなどと
呼ばれていますが　ここのところ→
負け続きで　全然ダメダメ。
正直もう　主人公とか→
But lately he's been losing left
and right! Totally worthless.
Isn't it absurd to even call him
the main character these days?
名乗るのも　おこがましいのでは
ないでしょうか？よって！→
私は彼に　チュパチュパチュパ
カブラスの形を求刑します！
So I recommend a sentence of the
chupachupachupacabrus penalty!
チュパチュパチュパ…ブラスの
刑ってなんだよ？
What's the chupachupachu... ...brus penalty?!
（東条）≪ちょっと待った～！≫
Hold it right there!
（古市）ウルトラ検察官　東条君。
Ultra-policeman Tojo-kun!
ウルトラ検察官って何だ？
What the hell's an ultra-policeman?
（東条）チュパチュパ　ラ…
カブラスの刑とは。
The chupachupa...chupacabrus penalty is...
言えてねえだろ　それ！
You couldn't say it!
そもそもお前　調子に
乗ってんじゃねえぞ！
Ain't you gettin' ahead of yourself?
そんなに負け続けるんなら
石矢魔最強は→
If you keep losin', how about you
give up being Ishiyama's strongest?
返上してもらおうか
という意味で。
それ　ただの
お前の要求じゃねえか！
That's what it means.
That's just your demands!
裁判長　お腹が…。
Your Honor... My stomach...
異議なし！
No objections!
おめえら黙ってろ！
べっ　弁護人　弁護人反論を！
Shut up you people!
Counsel! Counsel, object!
ムリです…。
お前かよ！行けよ　トイレ！
Not happening...
You?!
くそっ　誰かほかに　いないのか？
俺の弁護をする奴！誰でもいい！
Go to the bathroom!
Damn it... Isn't there
anyone else to defend me?
Anyone'll do!
全員こっち向け！コラッ！
Look at me in the face, people!
何を言ってるのやら…弁護人なら
いるではないですか→
What are you saying?
You've had someone to defend you
right by your side this whole time.
ずっと　あなたの側に。
ダッダッダッ…ビー！
（古市）弁護人　ベル坊君！
Counsel Baby Beel-kun!
だ…だめだ。せめて　しゃべれる人を
しゃべれる人を　お願いします！
I'm screwed...
At least someone that can talk!
Please, someone that can talk!
どわぁぁ～っ！イヤだ～！
チュパチュパチュパカブラスの刑はイヤだ～！
No!
I don't wanna face the
chupachupachupacabrus penalty!
俺は無実だぁ～！
I'm innocent!
ハッ！
グー　スピー…。
オープニングまで　なげえよ。
Get to the opening already.
はあ…ああクソ　もうヤダ
なんだよ→
Damn it all...
What the hell is the chupachupachupacabrus
penalty anyway?
チュパチュパチュパ
カブラスの刑って。
あい？ア　ダブ！
お～　おやつは５００円までだぞ。
大体なんだよ　あの弁護人→
Sure. No more than 500 yen for snacks.
And what was with my defense counsel?
弁護する気とか　全然ねえだろう。
He didn't seem to want to defend me at all!
アダダ…。
アダダ…ダーブ　ダー！
お～　バナナもＯＫだぞ。
ダーブ！
Sure, go for some bananas.
モンキーバナナでも　いいぞ。
ダダダ…ダブー？
Señorita bananas are fine, too.
おう。
ダダダ…ダブ　ダー！
Sure.
おう！
ダーブ！
Okay.
わぁ～っ！！
ダー！
What the heck?!
なんじゃこりゃぁ～！
Where Did Brother Disappear to?
《オッス　俺の名は　古市貴之。
自称イケメン高校生だ。→
Why, hello there. My name
is Furuichi Takayuki.
I'm a self-styled high-school heartthrob.
おいおい　自称イケメンって
悲しすぎるだろう　だって？→
Oh? Calling myself a heartthrob
is just sad, you say?
いいんだぜ　いつだって　自称は
外してもらって…君次第さ。→
Fine by me, I can call myself anything...
Anything you want...
あっ　すいません　待って！
本題に入るから！→
Wait, I'm sorry! I'll get to
the point, just keep listening!
もうちょっとだけ聞いて！》
Lately, aren't I a little out of the loop?
《な～んつって　なんつって！
言ってみただけ！→
Did I just say that? I totally said that!
Just threw that out there.
もう１人の　ちょっぴり拗ねた俺が
言ってみただけでガンス》
Just li'l ol' me feelin'
sorry for m'sel', 'tis.
（ラミア）古市！古市！
《ナハハのハーッ　てか？》
Buwahaha, amirite?
（ラミア）古市！
《さ…寂しい人じゃないもん》
I-I'm not lonely.
（ラミア）起きなさい！古市！
Wake up! Furuichi!
あ…あ。
ったく　相変わらずキモイわね。
何がナハハのハーッよ。
You're even creepy when you're asleep.
Buwahaha? What's that for?
さっさと起きて　支度しなさい！
今から私と→
Get up and get ready this instant!
Because you and I are going to
go search for Lord En, right now!
焔王ぼっちゃま
捜しに行くんだから！
夢か…。どうせなら
ヒルダさん出て来てください。
A dream, huh?
Please, let me dream of Hilda-san instead...
う～っ…起きろっつってんだろ
キモ男！！
I told you to wake up, creeper!
はあ？ベル坊の兄貴を捜す？
俺が　なんで？
Look for Baby Beel's brother?
Why me?
私１人じゃ　無理だからに
決まってんでしょ！
Because I can't handle it by myself, duh!
いや　だから何で俺？
つ～か　何で捜すの？
Yeah, but why me?
And why are we searching for him?
はぁ…あなた
何にも知らないのね。
You don't know anything, do you?
うわっ傷つく！何かその言い方
傷つくでガンスよ。
Man, that hurts!
The way you said it... Ouch.
何かあったの？ねえ　俺の
知らない間に　何か起こったの？
Did something happen?
Hey, did something happen
without me realizing it?
ちょっと　引っ張らないでよ！
きもいわね！→
Hey, don't pull that!
You are such a creep! Let go!
離しなさい！キャーッ！
（古市）ウワーッ！
（ほのか）お兄ちゃん
いつまで寝てるのよ？→
How long are you going to sleep?
いくら日曜日だからって
朝ごはん片付けてくれないと…。
I know it's Sunday, but if I
don't clean up breakfast...
ヒャッ！
あ…。
ロリコン…変態。
Lolicon...
Pervert!
（古市）ちょ　違う。これは…。
N-No! This isn't what you...
お　お母さんに　言わなきゃ…。
I've... gotta tell Mom...
（古市）てゆ～か　リアルな
リアクションやめて！
Come on, stop with the realistic reaction!
そ…そうね　まず警察に。
T-That's right...
First, call the police.
もっとリアルな話　やめて…。
That's an even more real reaction!
どいて古市！めんどくさいわね！
記憶消しましょ！
Get off me, Furuichi!
This is gonna be a pain...
Let's erase her memories!
人の妹に　なに
注射しようとしてんだぁ！
What the hell are you trying to
shoot into my little sister?!
（早乙女）というわけだ。お前も
悪魔にからまれて→
And that's how it is.
You must have had it rough, getting
involved with those Demons.
災難だったな。
う～ん　よく分からんが
禅さんは→
I don't really get it. You know him, Zen-san?
奴らのこと　知ってんのか？
何回　同じ説明させる気だよ。
だ～か～ら　あいつらは悪魔で…。
How many times are you going
to make me explain this?
I'm telling you that they were Demons!
おう　悪魔のように強かったぞ！
Yeah, he was as strong as a Demon.
じゃなく　悪魔なの！
禅さんの知り合いか？
No, he was a real Demon (akuma)!
Zen-san, you know him?
知り合いじゃねえよ！
違うのか…。
No, I don't know him!
You don't?
そこは　どうでも
いいんだよ！どうでも！
Who cares one way or the other?
ふぅ…分かってんのか？お前
一歩間違えたら死んでたんだぞ。→
Understand? If you had made
one wrong move you'd be dead.
見境なく　ケンカ
売ってんじゃねえよ。
Don't just go fighting indiscriminately!
ハハ…何言ってんだ禅さん。
What are you talking about, Zen-san?
He's human just like the rest of us.
同じ人間じゃねえか。
次は負けねえよ。
I won't lose next time.
悪魔だっつってんだろ！
I told you, he's a Demon (akuma)!
バカか？バカなのか　お前？
いやバカだったな　すまん。
Are you... Are you an idiot?
Oh. Right. You are an idiot. Sorry...
とにかく　相手は悪魔だ。
ア・ク・マ！
Anyway, you were up against
a Demon. A Demon (akuma)!
分かったら　もう
からむんじゃねえぞ！
If you get that, then don't
tangle with them again!
うんうん…熊ね。
Ah... Kuma (bear).
ガーッ！
で　どこ行ったら
もう一回戦えんだ？
So, where can I go to fight him again?
（早乙女）トラ。
Tora.
ま　関わっちまったものは
しょ～がねえわな。
I guess you gotta be involved now.
分かったよ　俺が教えてやる
悪魔との戦い方。→
Fine then, I get it. I'll
teach you how to fight Demons.
だから　もう無茶すんな。
フン！
So don't do anything crazy.
マジかよ？焔王の部下が
男鹿を殺しに来て→
Seriously?
Lord En's servants came to crush
Oga, and Hilda-san got stabbed?
ヒルダさんが刺された！？
おいおい　俺の知らない内に→
Man... I can't believe this serious turn
of events happened without me knowing.
なんちゅうシリアス展開だよ。
てゆ～か　ヒルダさん無事なのか？
Anyway, is Hilda-san okay?
The Doctor and I came for her, so yeah, duh!
私と師匠が来たんだから
無事に決まってるでしょ。
そんなことより
焔王ぼっちゃまよ！
Anyway, look for Lord En!
You met him, right? Do you have
any idea where he might be?
あんた　会ったでしょ？
どっか行きそうな場所とか→
心当たり　ないの？
あ～　会ったっつってもなぁ。
ゲームセンターとか？
Yeah, I guess I met him... Like, an arcade?
（ラミア）ゲームセンター…
何よ　それ？
Arcade?
What's that?
つ～かさ　何で俺なの？
さっきも聞いたけど。
Anyway, why me?
I asked you earlier...
しょ…しょうがないでしょ！
こっちで知ってんの→
I don't have any choice! You're the
only person who knows this place!
あんたしか　いないし！
つべこべ言わずに
付き合いなさいよ！
Stop complaining and come with me!
Huh? What's this? Tsundere?
《あれ　何これ　ツンデレ？
心細いのね　要するに。→
So basically, she's helpless.
ま　ちょっとぐらい
協力してやるか》
Well, I guess I could help her out a little.
ん？俺しか？
The only person?
Hold it. I'm not the only person.
待て待て　俺しかって
ことは　ないだろう。
当の男鹿本人は
どうしたよ？
What about Oga himself?
You really are out of the loop, aren't you?
（ラミア）あんた　本当に
何も聞いてないのね。
Hey! Stop talking like that!
ちょっ…また　その言い方
やめて　傷つくから。
I'm very sensitive!
（古市）邦枝先輩と
デート…だと？
On a date with Kunieda-senpai?!
いや　修業だってば。
No, I said they're training.
納得しないぞ！何だ　この差は！
I refuse to accept this! Why
does he get Kunieda and I get...
はぁっ？差？
どういう意味よ！
Get what, huh?!
What's that supposed to mean?!
ダーブ！アイー…。
重っ！それにしても
荷物デカ過ぎだろ。
But. yeah. You've got way too much stuff.
（邦枝）遅い！
You're late!
My bad. Stuff happened.
わりぃ！何か色々あった。
We're not heading to play
around, so keep sharp!
遊びに行くんじゃないんだから
しゃきっとしなさいよね！
う…おぉ。
Okay...
（邦枝祖父）お前こそ何じゃ！その
チャラついた格好は。
And what's with you and those flashy clothes?
別に…いつも通りですけど！
I-I'm no different than usual!
Mapputatsu?
（黒木）魔二津…？というと→
It's been a training grounds
since long ago, I hear.
古くから伝わる修業場ですね。
そこへ向かっているんですか？
That's where we're headed?
Yes. It's a bit far, but a
good place to temper the body.
（祖父）
うむ。ちと遠いが
身が引き締まる良い場所じゃ。
《なんで　この人達までいるの…》
Why are these people here too?
（三鏡）邦枝ちゃん　そのおにぎり
俺も　もらっていい？
Kunieda-chan, can I have
one of those onigiri?
う…うん…。
ヒョー！うんめぇ～！！
超うめぇ～！
Delish! Super delish!
Mikagami, that's not fair!
（鬼塚）あっ　三鏡　ズルいぞ！わしにも　よこせ！！
Let me have one, too!
And one for me.
（黒木）私にも。
Hey, Oga, listen up! We might be training
together but we're still enemies, got it?
言っとくけどな　男鹿！
一緒に修業はするが→
俺達　敵同士だからな。
Man, you guys are loud.
《うるせ～やつだな…》
Whoa, these are crazy good.
つ～か　マジうめぇ！
You'll make someone a
great bride, Kunieda-chan!
邦枝ちゃんは
いいお嫁さんになるわ。絶対！
For sure!
ど　ど～も…。
T-Thanks...
（出崎）キィー！何なの　あの女！！
What's with that woman?!
She's makin' googly eyes at my Ko-chan!
あたしの孝ちゃんに
色目使って…！
Don't go gettin' ideas from a single onigiri!
おにぎりぐらいで
いい気になってんじゃないわよ！
This is gonna be a slog.
《ドロ沼じゃな…》
Just a little more... A little more...
（ラミア）もうちょっと…
もうちょっとよ。→
もうちょっと…そこ！
A little more...
There!
Okay, here it comes!
よ～し　キタキタ…。→
おお～！
キタ！キタキタキタキタ…
キターッ！
Got it! Got it, got it, got it, got it!
We got it!
とったど～！やったぁ～！！
All right!
（古市）
って　俺　１５００円も使って
何してんの…？
...what did I just spend 1500 yen on?
（ラミア）はぁ…焔王ぼっちゃまを捜してるんじゃない。
I thought we were searching for Lord En.
Did you forget?
忘れたの？ったく…
しっかりしなさいよね！
Man, get a grip already. We're
not here to play around.
遊びに来たんじゃ
ないんだから！
Let's go.
行くわよ！エヘヘ…。
《だから
何なんだ　その態度はぁっ！？》
What is with that attitude?
Seriously, what? A date? Is it a date?
《何だこれ…
デート？デートなの！？》
I know I told her I'd help, but...
《確かに　協力するとは
言ったけどさぁ…》
《ハッ！いかん！
いかんぞ　貴之！！》
You can't! This is bad, Takayuki!
You look just like a lolicon!
《これでは　まるで
ロリコンみたいじゃないか！！》
That's really bad in this day and age!
《この　ご時世に
それは　マズい…》
No! This isn't that at all!
《違う！断じて違うぞ！！俺は→
I... I love Hilda-san's ample thighs!
俺はヒルダさんの
太ももが大好きだぁ～っ！！→
え～と　え～と　え～と
ヒルダさんなら…》
Um, um, um... Hilda-san...
Oh, silly Takayuki-san...
What am I to do with you?
もう　貴之さんったら
イケナイ人！
《いかん！もう１回だ…》
No! Try again...
Hilda-san, Hilda-san...
《ヒルダさん　ヒルダさん…》
Don't forget... We're
not here to play around.
言っておくが…
遊びに来たわけではないぞ。
《ああ…これこれ　これだよ…》
きもっ！
Yeah... That's the stuff...
Ew.
おお　牛じゃ！
どこよ　ここ！？
いい所ですね。
It's cows!
Look at this place...
Quiet...
Nice place.
（古市）だいたい　自分で言っといてなんだけど→
I should tell you that a kid like him wouldn't
be in this place in the middle of the day.
こんな所に真っ昼間から　あの
ちびっ子がいるわけないじゃん。
Really?
（ラミア）そうなの？
（古市）そうだよ。→
Yeah.
こんな早い時間に
ゲーセン来るのは→
The only people who'd come
this early to an arcade
are the dregs of society and lazy-ass
high school kids with nothin' to do.
せいぜい　やる事のない
高校生かダメ社会人くらいだ。→
俺に言わせりゃ　こんなとこ
だめんずの巣窟…ゲッ！？
Just my opinion, but these places
are the hangouts of losers.
おう　古市じゃねぇか。
お前もメダルゲームか？
Oh, it's Furuichi.
Playin' for tokens like me?
《うわぁ…だめんず　いた…》
And looks like we've got loser #1.
A brat with green hair?
（神崎）緑色の頭したガキ？
ああ　見たぜ。
うそっ！
Sure, I've seen him.
No way!
After all, this is my castle.
何せ　ここは
俺様の城だからな。
I totally remember anyone who stands out.
目立つ奴は
たいがい覚えてるよ。
So where was he?
それで　どこに？
Come with me.
ついて来な。
He's come here a lot recently.
（神崎）ここんとこ
よく来てたからな。→
Over there. Over there
at the fighting games...
ほら　そこだ。
そこの格ゲーの対戦機で…。
（由加）ぐわぁ～！！→
I lost again?! What's with
this guy? He's crazy!!
また負けた！
何じゃこいつは…パネェ～！！
んっ？
およっ　神崎先輩！
Kanzaki-senpai?
Why are you in my castle, crazy bitch?!
（神崎）パー子！なんで　てめえが
俺の城にいるんだ！？
What, you a fan? A fan of mine now?
あれか？ファンか？
ファンなのか？
いやいやいや…たまたまッス。
ってか　パー子じゃないッス！
No, no, no... Just by accident.
And I ain't a crazy bitch!
（由加）緑色のガキ？→
A brat with green hair?
Naw, ain't seen him. Is he an earthling?
いやぁ　見てないッスね。
地球人ッスか？
省略しすぎだ。何だよ
緑色のガキって。こえ～よ！
Fill me in more.
Green haired kid? What
the hell, that's scary!
《ヒマ人ばっかだな　石矢魔…》
Ishiyama's just full of
people with free time...
It's a pair of losers!
《もうちょっとで
勢揃いじゃね～か…？》
ゲーム強いんスか？そいつ。
もしかして→
Is he good at games?
What if he's the guy I was fighting against?!
うちが戦ってた相手だったりして。緑色ッスかねぇ？
Green hair, right?
（姫川）ああ？誰が緑色だ　コラ。
Who're you callin' green-haired, huh?
（古市）《だめんず揃った～！》
It's a full house of losers!
Rock, paper, scissors!
（三鏡・鬼塚・出崎）
ジャンケンポン！あいこでしょ！あいこでしょ…！
Tied! Tied again! Tied again!
ゲームセンター…。
An arcade...
そこに焔王ぼっちゃまが
いるというのか？
Is that where Lord En is?
No. They don't seem to have found him yet.
いえ…まだ見つかっては
いないそうですがね。
But Miss Lamia is really trying.
しかし　やりますなぁ
ラミア嬢は。→
It seems like she's using Takayuki and
the other Ishiyama people to search.
貴之や石矢魔の面々を使って
捜査に当たるそうです。→
This way they might really find
Lord En in the next few days.
これなら本当に数日中に→
焔王ぼっちゃまを
見つけるかもしれません。
Yes... So Furuichi's first name is Takayuki?
ふむ…貴之というのは
古市の下の名前だったか？
えっ！まっ　あらやだ…。
Oh, my! It was slip! I just
called him like I usually...
私ったら
ついつい　いつものクセで→
呼んでしまいました
お恥ずかしい…。
How embarrassing!
I-It's not like I'm against
her, or jealous or anything...
あっ　いえ　別に対抗心とか嫉妬心なんてものじゃないんですよ。
The bond between Takayuki and myself is
already so thick, there's no room for Miss Lamia!
私と貴之の間には　もはや→
ラミア嬢が入る余地は
ないほどに濃密な…。
うむ　傷に障る。黙れ！
ぐぐっ…。
Yes. You're making the pain worse. Shut up.
So...
しかし…そうか　ラミアは
上手くやってくれているのか。
I see. Lamia is doing well then?
So we have 5 days until Behemoth's
minions come to attack again?
ベヘモット達が再び
攻めてくるまで　残り５日か。
頼んだぞ…。
We're counting on you...
Hey, four-eyed freak! Why do I
keep meetin' you here every time?!
クソメガネ…
なんで　毎回毎回→
ここで　てめえに会うんだよ！
ぼっこぼこに　されて～か！？
You wanna get beat?!
Sure, let's do this.
ああ？やってみろよ！
Now that I think about it, we never
finished things from the last time.
そ～いや　てめえとの決着は
まだ　つけてなかったよな。
この際だ　どっちが上か→
I think it's just about time we
settled which one of us is on top.
ハッキリさせとこうじゃねぇか。
おもしれぇ。
Sounds like fun.
（ゲーム音声）レディー　ファイト！
（古市）いや　ゲームでつけるんスかこの決着…。
Oh. So they meant at this game.
何　この人達…。
Who are these people? Fine
then, leave this to me.
しょうがないわね　任せて！
（古市）いや　任せん！
大丈夫よ。薬打ち込むだけだから。
No, not leaving it to you!
Don't worry, I'm just going
to shoot them with this drug.
It'll make them feel a bit better,
and make them obey my every command.
ちょっと気持ち良くなって
操り人形みたいになるやつ。
えっ　全然　大丈夫じゃねぇっ！！
That's totally not okay! It
sounds extremely dangerous!
危ねぇ匂い
プンプンじゃね～か！
失礼ね　危なくないわよ。
That's rude of you. There's nothing
dangerous about it... ...almost nothing.
そんなには…。
They'll be released after half a day...
半日もすれば
解放されるんだから。
...from this mortal coil, that is...
この世の　しがらみとかから…。
死んでるよね！？それ
操られた挙句　死んでるよね！！
You mean they'll die? They'll
be slaves, and then they'll die?
Crap, she's serious.
《マズい…この子　本気だ…》
Hanasawa-san! Hanasawa-san!
花澤さん　花澤さん！うち？
Huh? Me?
What? Search for a kid?
（寧々）はぁ？子供を捜してる！？
There's no time for that!
I'm looking for Madam Aoi!
それどころじゃないわよ！
こっちだって→
姐さん　捜してんだから。
[TEL]（由加）いないんスか？
What's up?
She ain't at home, her cellphone's
in an area with no service,
家に行ってもいないし
携帯は圏外だし→
and we haven't seen her in two whole days!
もう丸２日会ってないのよ！
ど～なってんのよ！？
What the hell happened?
（邦枝）へ～くしっ！
うわぁ～！！
三鏡！
姐さんの居場所を知ってる！？
You know where she is?
ちょっと　どういう事？
どうして　あんたが！？
Hey, what's going on? Why do you know that?
Anyway, will you come over so I can explain?
[TEL]（古市）
あ…とりあえず説明するんで
来てもらえますか？
（古市）というわけで　今日皆さんに集まってもらったのは→
So let's start.
The reason I've gathered
you all here today...
他でもない　とある人物を
手分けして捜し出すためです。
It's to split up and search
for a certain individual.
（姫川）おいおい　古市よぉ。
Sheesh, Furuichi. Are you
asking for a beating?
てめえ
ぶっつぶされてぇのか？
That's your reason for getting in the
way of our battle and asking us here?
勝負の邪魔してまで
俺達を　こんな所につれて来た。
それが理由か？
（夏目）同感だね。
Agreed.
Furuichi-kun, you really shouldn't
start thinking you're in charge now.
古市君　あまり
調子に乗っちゃダメだよ。
You're basically trying to use us?
君　それ　俺達を
アゴで使おうってわけ？
んな事は　ど～でもいいのよ！
Who cares! I want to know
where Madam Aoi is! Now!
葵姐さんは
どこなのよ！？姐さんは。
もちろん　皆さんには
無関係じゃありません。
Of course, this does affect everyone.
To be precise, this is a problem
facing Ishiyama's reputation.
っていうか　これはむしろ
石矢魔の沽券に関わる問題です。
Not that reputation!
股間じゃないから！
ちょっと！
大丈夫なの？適当な事言って。
Hey, are you sure you should
just be winging this?
What else can we do? We've gotta make
this a problem for all of Ishiyama!
しょうがね～だろ！
こうなりゃ→
もう　石矢魔全体の問題に
するしかね～じゃね～か！
《大丈夫だ　勝算はある。
ナメられてると知ったら→
Don't worry, this can work.
These people really hate
being looked down on.
途端に団結するからな
この人達》
先日　男鹿と邦枝先輩が→
The other day Oga and Kunieda-senpai
were attacked by an unknown group.
何者かによって
襲撃を受けました。→
幸い２人とも無事でしたが
相手は信じられないほど強く→
Thankfully, the two of them were safe, but
the person they fought was incredibly strong.
あの男鹿ですら
勝つ事はできませんでした。
Even Oga wasn't able to win.
しかも　そいつら最後に→
And when it was over they said
"Ishiyama ain't so tough after all!"
「石矢魔なんて
全然　大した事ね～な→
"Ho-hohn! I fart in your general direction!"
へっへ～んだ！おならプー」って。
ああ？
あん？
むむ！？
クッ…！！
そんな奴らが
今度は　この石矢魔に→
They will be coming in full force
next time to attack Ishiyama.
本格的に攻めてくる
というのです。近いうちに。
And soon.
（寧々）ちょ　ちょっと待って。
それで　姐さんは？
Wait a sec. Where's Madam Aoi?
The two of them, knowing there's little time,
seem to have started training in a certain place.
力のなさを実感した２人は→
とある場所で
特訓を始めるそうです。
Training?
（寧々）特訓！？
はい。
Yes. I'm sure they will
grow stronger and return.
あの２人は
必ず成長して帰ってきます。
That's why I'm asking you,
not for me, but for Ishiyama!
だから　誰のためでもない
石矢魔のために　お願いします！
先輩達に　その首謀者を
捜し出してほしいんです！！
I need you all to find their ringleader!
So? Maybe it's a little much...
《どうだ…やっぱ苦しいか？》
Were they wearing some
weird uniform with a coat?
（神崎）
もしかして　そいつら
妙なコートの制服着てなかったか？
だったら　俺も
やりあったぜ。なぁ　パー子。
In that case I fought with
'em too. Right, crazy bitch?
は　はい！
（寧々）由加。
Y-Yeah!
Yuka...
I totally saw 'em by accident!
They were crazy, all right.
いや　うちも偶然見たんスけど
マジパネェっすよ。→
あの東条先輩も　ぼっこぼこに
やられてましたから。
Even Tojo-senpai got beat to a pulp!
《ミラクル　キターッ！！》
It's a miracle!
前に言ってた奴らの事か…。
The guys you mentioned before?
Tojo was beat up, that's true.
確かに東条の野郎
ボロボロだったなぁ…。
Yes, yes, yes!
《キタキタキターッ！》
どこの学校よ？
（古市）《キタ　コレーッ！！》
Which school was it?
Yes, here we go!
この辺の奴らじゃねぇ。
たぶん修学旅行生とかだぜ。
They weren't from around here.
Probably here on a trip or something.
They said something about being "akuma"?
「アクマ」が　どうとか
言ってたけど。
悪魔ぁ？
Akuma?
Yeah, they were totally as strong as a demon!
いや　マジ悪魔みたいに
パネェ強かったんスよ。
Either way, we can't have
people looking down on us.
何にしても　ナメられっぱなし
ってわけにも　いかねぇな。
《ふぅん…やるじゃん》
Nice going.
（バン！）
その名も…悪魔野学園！！
They are from... Akumano Academy!
ええっ！？
あくまの…。がくえん…。
Akumano...
...Academy?
Hey, you're gettin' carried away!
That's seriously not gonna...
《ちょっとぉ～！！
調子に乗り過ぎでしょう。→
いくらなんでも　それは…》
なんて
悪そうな名前の学校だ！
I've never heard a school
whose name sounded so evil!
We'll crush them!
俺達が　ぶっ潰してやんぜ！
えっ…ヘヘヘヘ…。
（三鏡）ヒィーッ！！
（鬼塚）オ～ッ！（出崎）ギャー！
（黒木）うわ～！！
前来た時　絶対こんな道じゃ
なかっただろぉぉ～！！
I so totally didn't come up this way before!
ふぉっふぉっふぉっふぉ！
Take the long road, I say.
遠回りさせてやったわい。
What are you doing, Oga?
While we're desperately
searching for Lord En,
you're doing special "muhuhu"
training with Kunieda-senpai!
What kind of training is "muhuhu" training?
Well, obviously:
"No, Oga. It goes like this. Do it stronger.
Yes, like that. Very good... Ah!"
...like that. And then things get all
excited when your elbow touches her boob!
Ew.
On the next Beelzebub:
I Must Become Stronger.
Then, their two faces get close, and...
Cut it out already!